Youssef el attar

10 Daneshill House, 1 Waterloo Road, Uxbridge, UB8 2FD youssettar@gmail.com 07732 790 081

GITHUB PROFILE LINKEDIN PROFILE HYPERIONDEV PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

Results-driven professional with over 6 years of managerial and security expertise, showcasing a clear, logical mindset and a practical problem-solving approach. Known for delivering exceptional customer service standards and successfully leading teams across diverse sectors. Currently enrolled in an intensive Software Engineering Bootcamp, demonstrating a commitment to continuous learning and a keen focus on mastering advanced technical skills.

EXPERIENCE

Software engineering, hyperiondev — 2023 December – 2024 march

- Capstone projects.
- Defensive and logical programming.
- IO Operations.
- Object Orientated Programming.

Security officer, Cromwell Hospital — 2022-current

Ensuring safety and security of hospital, staff, patients, and visitors.

- Monitoring CCTV cameras.
- Responding to emergencies.
- Handling all security-related duties.
- Operating the switchboard.
- Responding to incoming calls on out-of-hours.
- Directing calls to appropriate departments or personnel.

SHIFT LEADER, GETIR — 2021-2022

Getir is a Turkish company that offer an on-demand "ultrafast" delivery service for grocery items.

- Managing 80+ staff members.
- Enhancing customer satisfaction.
- Overseeing health and safety.
- Meeting sales and profitability goals.
- Managing staff effectiveness.

GYM MANAGER, URBAN KINGS GYM — 2014-2021

Initially started as a receptionist who handled member inquiries and provided excellent customer service. After a year I was offered a position as a manager and my responsibilities expanded to:

- Oversight of trainers, staff, housekeeping, and gym members.
- Ensuring effective communication and coordination.
- Managing daily gym operations.
- Focused on enhancing member experience.
- Drive membership sales and meet enrolment targets.

Security officer, profile protection — 2016-2021

I had a chance to be employed by a prestigious security company and accumulate 5 years of consistent experience.

- Worked in exclusive venues in London such as Scandal, Toyroom, 100 Wardour St., Quaglinos, Kadie's etc.
- Diligently fulfilled duties, ensuring compliance with security standards.
- Emergency response planning.
- Dealing with conflicts or disturbances to handle disputes and maintain a safe environment.

Sales assistant, atentó, Tetouan, morocco — 2012-2014

Worked at ATENTO, a Spanish phone sales and marketing company based in Tetouan, Morocco. Company focused on providing a cost-effective alternative for various European countries.

- Following the week's planning and studying market strategy.
- Providing customer assistance and making sales for selected products.
- Collaborating with top companies across Europe.
- Role involved a combination of strategic planning, customer service and sales activities.

EDUCATION

I.E.S THIAR, ALICANTE, SPAIN — GSCS, 2004-2008. Software Engineering, HYPERION DEV 2023-2024

SKILLS

Multilingual speaking (English, Spanish, Arabic, Dutch, and French) - Attention to detail Emotional intelligence - Organisational skills - Problem-solving - Critical thinking

ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- Full UK Driving license
- •Door Supervisor badge
- •GDPR Certificate

- First aids Certificate
- •Fire Safety Certificate
- •Food Safety Certificate